<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Universal</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Universal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Scraping Tutorial</title>
      <link>/post/web-scraping-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/web-scraping-tutorial/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help and would love to work together! Are you curious about something? Please feel free to contact us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>The Team Rita Sekkat Rita is one of the five founders of HAPPIH. She grew up in Morocco before coming to France. She is currently student at Sciences Po Paris in Master of public policy and she is doing the gender equality and public policy certificate between Sciences Po and Harvard. She is committed in favor of women’s right. She aims to reduce gender inequality towards the world and break down the menstruation taboo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/</guid>
      <description>#BeHappih, l’initiative estudiantine qui aborde sans tabou le sujet des règles « Humanitarian Action for Protection and Preservation of Intimate Hygiene » (HAPPIH) est le nom de l’initiative portée par cinq étudiants de Sciences Po Paris avec le soutien de la Direction de la coopération internationale de Monaco (DCI). Un projet pilote au Maroc entrepris par Charles Culioli, Walid Ben Hamadi, Moez Rais, Rita Sekkat et Denizalp Goktas, originaires de différents pays notamment du royaume.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>/news.utf8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news.utf8/</guid>
      <description>#BeHappih, l’initiative estudiantine qui aborde sans tabou le sujet des règles « Humanitarian Action for Protection and Preservation of Intimate Hygiene » (HAPPIH) est le nom de l’initiative portée par cinq étudiants de Sciences Po Paris avec le soutien de la Direction de la coopération internationale de Monaco (DCI). Un projet pilote au Maroc entrepris par Charles Culioli, Walid Ben Hamadi, Moez Rais, Rita Sekkat et Denizalp Goktas, originaires de différents pays notamment du royaume.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>